export const Questions = [
  {
    question:
      'Due to the essential nature of washing your hands, how much time is recommended to wash your hands?',
    A: '10 seconds',
    B: '20 seconds',
    C: '1 minute',
    D: '4 minutes',
    answer: 'B',
    details:
      'Wet, apply soap and rub your hands together for a minimum of 20 seconds and then rinse with running water.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'A person has lost a large amount of blood, has pale skin, and is confused. What is the cause?',
    A: 'Seizure',
    B: 'Stroke',
    C: 'Low blood sugar',
    D: 'Shock',
    answer: 'D',
    details:
      'This is a classic presentation of shock because of blood loss and is a medical emergency. Other causes of shock include infection, severe allergic reactions, severe dehydration, and heart problems.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'While performing CPR on an infant, another rescuer appears on the scene. What do you do next?',
    A: 'Immediately transport the patient',
    B: 'Wait until exhausted, then switch',
    C: 'Have the second rescuer help with CPR, to minimize fatigue',
    D: 'Have the second rescuer begin ventilation ratio 30:2',
    answer: 'C',
    details:
      'The ratio of two-person CPR for infants and children is 15:2. One-person CPR for all ages is 30:2.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Where should you place the AED pads when treating an infant for pediatric cardiac arrest?',
    A: 'Chest and back',
    B: 'Do not use an AED on an infant',
    C: 'Upper chest and mid-abdomen',
    D: 'Wherever they fit',
    answer: 'A',
    details: 'Place pads on the chest and back on an infant.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How long should you check for breathing while performing CPR?',
    A: 'Do not check for breathing, continue chest compressions',
    B: '2 seconds',
    C: '5 seconds',
    D: 'No longer than 10 seconds',
    answer: 'D',
    details: 'Do not stop CPR for more than 10 seconds to check for breathing.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'After finding an unresponsive child, yelling for help, and confirming the child is not breathing, what would be your next course of action?',
    A: 'Leave the child and search for an AED',
    B: 'Deliver rescue breaths, most cardiac arrests occur due to breathing problems',
    C: 'Begin back blows and chest thrusts',
    D: 'Deliver 30 chest compressions',
    answer: 'D',
    details:
      'Do not leave the child. Beginning chest compressions is critical.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'When you try to give an unresponsive adult a rescue breath and the chest does not appear to rise, what would you do next?',
    A: 'Perform abdominal thrusts',
    B: 'Begin CPR',
    C: 'Go call 911',
    D: 'Repeat the head tilt/chin lift maneuver and attempt the breath again',
    answer: 'D',
    details:
      'Attempt a breath, and if it goes in, deliver a second breath. If unable to ventilate, assume an additional foreign body is present.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'You find someone unresponsive who has a pulse but not breathing. You are unable to give them CPR, what do you do next?',
    A: 'Begin CPR',
    B: 'Repeat the head tilt/chin lift maneuver and attempt the breath again',
    C: 'Abdominal thrusts',
    D: 'Heimlich maneuver',
    answer: 'B',
    details:
      'If unable to deliver the first breath, reposition the airway and attempt the breath again. It is safe to assume a form body is present and abdominal thrusts are indicated.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'You find an unresponsive person with no pulse. You can not do CPR. What would you do?',
    A: 'Wipe off the face or cover with a shirt',
    B: 'Compression only CPR',
    C: 'Go and get help',
    D: 'Do not initiate resuscitation',
    answer: 'B',
    details:
      'Only CPR has been shown to be effective. Leaving the victim significantly increases mortality.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the key action if someone is unresponsive and not breathing?',
    A: 'Give chest compressions',
    B: 'Raise their feet above their head',
    C: 'Try to breathe into their mouth',
    D: 'Raise their feet above their head',
    answer: 'A',
    details:
      'The key action is to give chest compressions. If we feel able to, we can give rescue breaths.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Someone has collapsed and is not breathing. You can tell this because his ‘what’ is not moving?',
    A: 'His stomach and shoulders',
    B: 'His chest and stomach',
    C: 'His mouth and cheeks',
    D: 'His shoulders and neck',
    answer: 'B',
    details:
      'If someone isn’t breathing, their chest and stomach will not be moving and you won’t hear or feel any signs of breaths.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'If someone is unresponsive and not breathing, how long should we give chest compressions?',
    A: 'Until your arms get tired',
    B: 'Until you have done 100 compressions',
    C: 'Until help arrives and someone else takes over',
    D: 'His shoulders and neck',
    answer: 'C',
    details:
      'There is no fixed number of chest compressions. If possible, keep giving chest compressions until help arrives',
  },
  {
    question:
      'noooooooo If someone is unresponsive and not breathing, how long should we give chest compressions?',
    A: 'Until your arms get tired',
    B: 'Until you have done 100 compressions',
    C: 'Until help arrives and someone else takes over',
    D: 'His shoulders and neck',
    answer: 'C',
    details:
      'There is no fixed number of chest compressions. If possible, keep giving chest compressions until help arrives',
  },
];
